Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Corporation Vertical Files, circa 1915-1999, bulk1960s-1990s RL.00678
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Corporation Vertical Files
circa 1915-1999, bulk 1960s-1990s
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.00678
43.1 Linear Feet
25,961 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. However, some of the materials in this collection are not immediately accessible, because they require further processing before use.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Corporation Vertical Files was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a transfer in 2000.
Historical Note
One of a series of vertical files maintained by JWT Information Center in Chicago Office over many decades.
Collection Overview
Alphabetical files of miscellaneous information about hundreds of mainly U.S. corporations, some of them domestic and many multinational. The fullest documentation tends to be for companies that are or have been JWT clients (notably Kraft, Quaker Oats, Sears, Ford, Northern Telcom, Gerber, Kellogg, Philip Morris, Oscar Mayer, Kemper, S.C. Johnson, McDonnell Douglas, Jos. Schlitz, 7-Up, and others) and several that are or were major competitors of JWT clients (e.g. AT&T, McDonald's, General Motors, among others). Files contain widely diverse formats of information including internal JWT unpublished reports and memoranda; many articles clipped from magazines (especially trade press) and newspapers; articles printed from computer databases; company publications and annual reports; historical booklets and articles; three vinyl record albums; and miscellaneous items. The richest files tend to be those for major JWT Chicago office accounts, with by far the greatest amount and diversity of information on Kraft. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising, and Marketing History.
Memoranda; Big business -- United States -- History; Corporate image -- United States -- History; Brand name products -- Marketing; Advertising -- United States -- History; Phonograph records; Clippings (information artifacts); Philip Morris and Company; Sears, Roebuck and Company; Quaker Oats Company; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; J. Walter Thompson Company; Kellogg Company; Johnson Wax; McDonald's Corporation; Kraft Foods Company; Northern Telecom Inc.; McDonnell Douglas Aerospace (Firm); AT and T.; Ford Motor Company; General Motors Company; Gerber Products Company; J. Walter Thompson Company; Oscar Mayer & Co
- Vertical File
  - A and W International, 1973-1989 (Box 1)
  - Ace Hardware, 1979-1992 (Box 1)
  - All American Gourmet Co., 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Alberto Culver, 1960-1992, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Allied Van Lines, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Altoids, 1979-1998 (Box 1)
  - American Cyanamid, 1969-1987 (Box 1)
  - American Express, 1979-1992 (Box 2)
  - American Motors, 1959-1985 (Box 2)
  - A.T. and T., 1962-1998, 1-5 of 15 folders (Box 2)
  - A.T. and T., 1962-1998, 6-12 of 15 folders (Box 3)
  - A.T. and T., 1962-1998, 13-15 of 15 folders (Box 4)
  - Ameritech, 1970-1997 (Box 4)
  - Ameritech, 1970-1997, 1-3 of 8 folders (Box 4)
  - Ameritech, 1970-1997, 4-8 of 8 folders (Box 5)
  - Amway, 1968-1983 (Box 6)
  - Anchor Brewing, 1977-1990 (Box 6)
  - Anheuser Busch, 1980-1990 (Box 6)
  - Apple Computer, 1984-1995 (Box 6)
  - Arby's Inc., 1976-1990 (Box 6)
  - Armour Co., 1962-1980 (Box 6)
  - Avon Corp., 1977-1995 (Box 6)
  - Banquet Foods, 1974-1980 (Box 6)
  - Baskin Robbins, 1978-1989 (Box 6)
  - Beatrice, 1969-1989, 1-2 of 6 folders (Box 6)
  - Beatrice, 1969-1989, 3-6 of 6 folders (Box 7)
  - Beatrice, 1969-1989 (Box 8)
  - Beatrice-Esmark, 1976-1985 (Box 8)
  - Beatrice-Tropicana, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Beech Nut Foods, 1964-1988 (Box 8)
  - Bell South, 1984-1993 (Box 8)
  - Ben and Jerry's, 1987-1993 (Box 8)
  - Benetton, 1983-1992 (Box 8)
  - Bic Corp, 1972-1977 (Box 8)
  - Big Boy, 1979-1988 (Box 9)
  - Blue Cross and Blue Shield, 1969-1992 (Box 9)
  - Booth Fisheries, 1956-1979 (Box 9)
  - Borden, 1943-1993, 5 folders (Box 9)
  - Braniff Airways, 1965-1992 (Box 9)
  - Braun, 1981-1990 (Box 9)
  - Bristol Myers, 1983-1996, 1 of 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Bristol Myers, 1983-1996, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Brookfield Zoo, 1989-1991 (Box 10)
  - Brunswick Corp., 1973-1982 (Box 10)
  - Burger Chef Systems, 1972-1980 (Box 10)
  - Burger King, 1974-1994, 4 folders (Box 10)
  - Burger King, 1984-1995 (Box 11)
  - Cadbury-Schweppes, 1973-1990 (Box 11)
  - Campbell Soup Co., 1969-1994, 5 folders (Box 11)
  - Campbell-Taggert Inc., 1967-1986 (Box 12)
  - Canada Dry, 1967-1990 (Box 12)
  - Carnation Co., 1976-1986 (Box 12)
  - Centel, 1981-1993 (Box 12)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. paul and Pacific R.R. Co., 1950-1981, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Chicago Tribune, 1969-1989 (Box 12)
  - Church's Fried Chicken, 1977-1989 (Box 12)
  - Church and Dwight Co., 1974-1994 (Box 12)
  - Clairol Inc., 1974-1989 (Box 12)
  - Coca-Cola, 1960-1996, 6 folders (Box 13)
  - Coca-Cola, 1960-1996, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Colgate-Palmolive, 1969-1974, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Coleman Co., 1966-1979 (Box 14)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., 1976-1987 (Box 14)
  - Computerland, 1983-1988 (Box 14)
  - Conagra Inc., 1982-1999, 5 folders (Box 15)
  - Adolph Coors Co., 1979-1992, 1-4 of 5 folders (Box 15)
  - Adolph Coors Co., 1979-1992, 5 of 5 folders (Box 16)
  - Corning Glass Works, 1976-1991 (Box 16)
  - Cotter and Co. (True Value), 1981-1992, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - CPC International, 1969-1995, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Helene Curtis, 1974-1988 (Box 16)
  - Dayton Hudson, 1979-1995 (Box 16)
  - Dean Foods, Inc., 1977-1987 (Box 17)
  - DeBeers, 1984 (Box 17)
  - Deere and Co., 1971-1993 (Box 17)
  - Del Monte Corp., 1975-1987 (Box 17)
  - Frances Denny, 1974-1979 (Box 17)
  - Walt Disney Co., 1971-1993, 1-3 of 6 folders (Box 17)
  - Walt Disney Co., 1971-1993, 4-6 of 6 folders (Box 18)
  - Domino's, 1986-1992 (Box 18)
  - Drackett Co., 1972-1993 (Box 18)
  - Dr. Pepper Co., 1971-1991 (Box 18)
  - Alfred Dunhill Ltd. 1976-1978 (Box 18)
  - Dunkin Donuts, Inc., 1974-1992 (Box 18)
  - Dunlop Corp., 1982-1984 (Box 19)
  - Eastern Airlines, 1975-1991 (Box 19)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1976-1994, 6 folders (Box 19)
  - Employers Mutuals of Wausau, Wisconsin, 1957-1973 (Box 19)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica Inc., 1968-1979 (Box 20)
  - Entemann's Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 20)
  - EPI Products, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Estee Lauder Inc., 1970-1988 (Box 20)
  - Exxon, 1974-1990 (Box 20)
  - Faberge Inc., 1977-1985 (Box 20)
  - Fairmont Foods Co., 1964-1981 (Box 20)
  - Falstaff Brewing Corp., 1960-1983 (Box 20)
  - Firestone Tire and Rubber Co., 1971 (Box 20)
  - First Federal Savings and Loan, 1960-1981 (Box 20)
  - FMC Corp., 1972-1974 (Box 20)
  - Ford Motor Co., 1950-1973, 1-4 of 20 folders (Box 20)
  - Ford Motor Co., 1974-1982, 5-12 of 20 folders (Box 21)
  - Ford Motor Co., 1983-1995, 13-17 of 20 folders (Box 22)
  - Ford Motor Co., 1950-1995, 18-20 of 20 folders (Box 23)
  - Friendly Ice Cream, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Frito-Lay, 1982-1992 (Box 23)
  - Fruit of the Loom, 1977-1990 (Box 23)
  - Fuller Brush Co., 1974-1987 (Box 23)
  - Ernest and Julio Gallo Winery, 1976-1987 (Box 23)
  - The Gap Stores, 1987-1992 (Box 23)
  - Gateway 2000, 1996-2000 (Box 24)
  - General Electric Co., 1980-1992 (Box 24)
  - General Foods, 1950-1992, 5 folders (Box 24)
  - General Mills, 1954-1996, 7 folders (Box 25)
  - General Motors, 1915-1995, 8 folders (Box 26)
  - Gerber, 1971-1996, 1-6 of 16 folders (Box 27)
  - Gerber, 1971-1996, 7-14 of 16 folders (Box 28)
  - Gerber, 1971-1996, 15-16 of 16 folders (Box 29)
  - Gillette, 1948-1996, 4 folders (Box 29)
  - Gino's, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Godfather's Pizza, 1981-1987 (Box 29)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co., 1973-1989 (Box 29)
  - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co., 1955-1997, 1 of 4 folders (Box 29)
  - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co., 1955-1997, 2-4 of 4 folders (Box 30)
  - Gould Inc., 1976-1987 (Box 30)
  - Goya Foods Inc., 1982-1991 (Box 30)
  - W.R. Grace and Co., 1977-1985 (Box 30)
  - Grand Metropolitan, 1984-1997, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box 30)
  - Grand Metropolitan, 1984-1997, 3 of 3 folders (Box 31)
  - The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co., 1949-1990, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Green Giant Co., 1956-1991 (Box 31)
  - Greyhound Corp., 1958-1989, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Hallmark Card Co., 1970-1987 (Box 32)
  - Hamburger Hamlet, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Theodore Hamm Co., 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Hammond Organ Co., 1966-1975 (Box 32)
  - Hanes, 1972-1980 (Box 32)
  - Hardee's Food Systems Inc., 1973-1993 (Box 32)
  - Harley-Davidson Motor Co., 1972-1999 (Box 32)
  - Harris Bankcorp, 1973-1993 (Box 33)
  - Hartmarx, 1974-1992, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Hartz Mountain Pet Foods Inc., 1972-1983 (Box 33)
  - Health and Tennis Corp., 1976-1988 (Box 33)
  - G. Heileman Brewing Co., 1975-1982, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Heineken, 1988-1993 (Box 33)
  - Heinz, 1964-1997, 1 of 6 folders (Box 33)
  - Heinz, 1964-1997, 2-6 of 6 folders (Box 34)
  - Hershey Foods Co., 1948-1993 (Box 34)
  - Hertz Corp., 1960-1992 (Box 34)
  - Heublein Inc., 1970-1982 (Box 35)
  - Hilton Hotels Corp., 1963-1991 (Box 35)
  - Charles E. Hires Co., 1951-1961 (Box 35)
  - Hoffman-LaRoche Inc., 1976-1980 (Box 35)
  - Holiday Inns of America Inc., 1963-1992 (Box 35)
  - The Hoover Co., 1954-1993 (Box 35)
  - Hormel and Co., 1947-1999, 4 folders (Box 35)
  - Houbigant, 1975 (Box 36)
  - Howard Johnson Co., 1963-1989 (Box 36)
  - Huber Brewing Co., 1973-1983 (Box 36)
  - Hunt-Wesson Foods, Inc., 1971-1984 (Box 36)
  - E.F. Hutton, 1977-1988 (Box 36)
  - Hyatt Hotels, 1977-1994, 1-5 of 8 folders (Box 36)
  - Hyatt Hotels, 1977-1994, 6-8 of 8 folders (Box 37)
  - Hyatt International Corp., 1978-1991 (Box 37)
  - IBM, 1976-1993, 5 folders (Box 37)
  - Ideal Toy Corp., 1978 (Box 38)
  - IGA, 1976-1986 (Box 38)
  - IMG, 1990-1999 (Box 38)
  - Inland Steel Co., 1969-1976 (Box 38)
  - Institute for Health Maintenance, 1982-1983 (Box 38)
  - Intel Corp., 1993-1997 (Box 38)
  - Interbrand, 1983 (Box 38)
  - Inter-Continental Hotels, 1984-1987 (Box 38)
  - International Dairy Queen, 1974-1982 (Box 38)
  - International Spike Corp., 1973-1983 (Box 38)
  - Interstate Bakeries Corp., 1964-1982 (Box 38)
  - Jacob Leinenkugel Brewing Co., 1978-1992 (Box 38)
  - Jay Foods Co., 1975-1986 (Box 38)
  - Jenny Craig, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Jeno's Inc., 1976-1984 (Box 38)
  - Jewel Companies, 1969-1992 (Box 38)
  - Jockey International Inc., 1974-1988 (Box 38)
  - Johnson and Johnson, 1977-1990 (Box 38)
  - Johnson Products Co., Inc., 1974-1990, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Johnson Publishing Co., 1975-1990 (Box 39)
  - S.C. Johnson and Sons, Inc., 1984-1989, 1-7 of 9 folders (Box 39)
  - S.C. Johnson and Sons, Inc., 1984-1989, 8-9 of 9 folders (Box 40)
  - Jordache, 1988-1992 (Box 40)
  - Jovan Co., 1975-1982, 3 folders (Box 40)
  - K Mart Co., 1977-1992, 3 folders (Box 41)
  - Keebler Co., 1969-1992 (Box 41)
  - Kellogg Co., 1942-1991, 1-4 of 12 folders (Box 41)
  - Kellogg Co., 1942-1991, 5-11 of folders (Box 42)
  - Kellogg Co., 1942-1991, 12 of 12 folders (Box 43)
  - Kemper, 1969-1995, 1-6 of 10 folders (Box 43)
  - Kemper, 1969-1995, 7-10 of 10 folders (Box 44)
  - Kentucky Fried Chicken, 1970-1991 (Box 44)
  - Kimberly-Clark, 1971-1992 (Box 44)
  - King's World / King's Island, 1974-1976 (Box 45)
  - Knudsen Corp., 1981-1988 (Box 45)
  - E.J. Korvette, 1974-1981 (Box 45)
  - Kraft, 1920-1999, 1-7 of 52 folders (Box 45)
  - Kraft, 1920-1999, 8-14 of 52 folders (Box 46)
  - Kraft, 1920-1999, 15-20 of 52 folders (Box 47)
  - Kraft, 1920-1999, 21-29 of 52 folders (Box 48)
  - Kraft, 1920-1999, 30-36 of 52 folders (Box 49)
  - Kraft, 1920-1999, 37-42 of 52 folders (Box 50)
  - Kraft, 1920-1999, 43-48 of 52 folders (Box 51)
  - Kraft, 1920-1999, 49-51 of 52 folders (Box 52)
  - Kraft, 1920-1999, 52 of 52 folders (Box 53)
  - La Quinta, 1986-1994 (Box 53)
  - Lever Bros., 1956-1992 (Box 53)
  - Libby, McNeill and Libby, 1959-1983, 2 folders (Box 53)
  - Thomas J. Lipton Co., 1963-1992 (Box 53)
  - Loblaw, 1989-1994 (Box 53)
  - Lorillard, 1960-1981 (Box 53)
  - Lowe's Companies, 1980-1995 (Box 53)
  - Lowenbrau, 1980-1991, 2 folders (Box 54)
  - McDonald's Corp., 1960-1996, 1-6 of 9 folders (Box 54)
  - McDonald's Corp., 1960-1996, 7-9 of 9 folders (Box 55)
  - McDonnell Douglas, 1970-1994, 1-3 of 14 folders (Box 55)
  - McDonnell Douglas, 1970-1994, 4-9 of 14 folders (Box 56)
  - McDonnell Douglas, 1970-1994, 10-14 of 14 folders (Box 57)
  - Marriott Corp., 1978-1992 (Box 57)
  - Mars Inc., 1977-1991 (Box 57)
  - Marshall Field and Co., 1958-1982 (Box 57)
  - Mattell Inc., 1971-1994 (Box 57)
  - MCI Communications, 1985-1998, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box 57)
  - MCI Communications, 1985-1998, 3 of 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Meijer, 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Mercedes Benz of North America, 1979-1987 (Box 58)
  - Merck and Co., 1969 (Box 58)
  - Meredith Corp., 1970-1985 (Box 58)
  - Merrill Lynch, 1977-1988 (Box 58)
  - Metropolitan Life, 1989-1995 (Box 58)
  - MFS Communications Co., 1994 (Box 58)
  - Midas International Corp., 1970-1995 (Box 58)
  - Midway Airlines 1981-1991 (Box 58)
  - Miller Brewing Co., 1956-1993, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Miller Brewing Co., 1956-1993, 3 of 3 folders (Box 59)
  - Mitsubishi, 1982-1992 (Box 59)
  - Mobil Corp., 1975-1990, 4 folders (Box 59)
  - Montgomery Wards, 1969-1991, 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Morton-Thiokol, 1965-1988 (Box 59)
  - Motorola, Inc., 1969-1995, 4 folders (Box 60)
  - Mrs. Smith's Pie Co., 1965-1981 (Box 60)
  - Munsingwear, 1981-1983 (Box 60)
  - Navistar, 1981-1988 (Box 60)
  - Neiman-Marcus, 1974-1988 (Box 60)
  - Nestle, 1966-1998, 1-2 of 4 folders (Box 60)
  - Nestle, 1966-1998, 3-4 of 4 folders (Box 61)
  - Nike Corp., 1983-1994 (Box 61)
  - Nintendo, 1989-1996, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Nissan, 1981-1990 (Box 61)
  - Northern Telecom (Nortel), 1979-1994, 1-2 of 16 folders (Box 61)
  - Northern Telecom (Nortel), 1979-1994, 3-8 of 16 folders (Box 62)
  - Northern Telecom (Nortel), 1979-1994, 9-14 of 16 folders (Box 63)
  - Northern Telecom (Nortel), 1979-1994, 15-16 of 16 folders (Box 64)
  - Northern Trust Co., 1984-1993 (Box 64)
  - Northwest Airlines, 1990-1992 (Box 64)
  - Northwestern Mutual Life, 1958-1998, 1-3 of 5 folders (Box 64)
  - Northwestern Mutual Life, 1958-1998, 4-5 of 5 folders (Box 65)
  - Nutrasweet, 1987-1992 (Box 65)
  - Ocean Spray Cranberries Inc., 1978-1983 (Box 65)
  - Oscar Mayer, 1958-1996, 1-3 of 10 folders (Box 65)
  - Oscar Mayer, 1958-1996, 4-9 of 10 folders (Box 66)
  - Oscar Mayer, 1958-1996, 10 of 10 folders (Box 67)
  - Otis Elevator (Box 67)
  - Pacific Telesis (Box 67)
  - Payless Shoe Source (Box 67)
  - J.C. Penney Co. (Box 67)
  - Pepsico, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box 67)
  - Pepsico, 3 of 3 folders (Box 68)
  - Perrier (Box 68)
  - Pfizer (Box 68)
  - Philip Morris, 1-4 of 11 folders (Box 68)
  - Philip Morris, 5-10 of 11 folders (Box 69)
  - Philip Morris, 11 of 11 folders (Box 70)
  - Pier 1 Imports (Box 70)
  - Pillsbury Inc., 1963-1992, 3 folders (Box 70)
  - Pizza Hut, 1975-1991 (Box 70)
  - Premier, 1990-1992 (Box 70)
  - Princess Cruises, 1988-1998 (Box 70)
  - Procter and Gamble, 1946-1994, 8 folders (Box 71)
  - Prudential Life Insurance Co., 1963-1994 (Box 72)
  - Quaker Oats, 1960-1980, 5 folders (Box 72)
  - Quaker Oats, 1981-1990, 6 folders (Box 73)
  - Quaker Oats, 1991-1995 and undated, 8 folders (Box 74)
    Scope and Contents note
    [Includes Aunt Jemima, Dog owners, Fisher Price, Gatorade, Willie Wonka, and market research]
  - Quaker Oats, publications and miscellaneous, 1960-1995, 6 folders (Box 75)
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA), 1974-1990 (Box 76)
  - Radisson Hotel Corp., 1989-1992 (Box 76)
  - Reebok, 1986-1991 (Box 76)
  - Revlon Inc., 1970-1993 (Box 76)
  - RJR Nabisco, 1968-1991, 1-3 of 4 folders (Box 76)
  - RJR Nabisco, 1968-1991, 4 of 4 folders (Box 77)
  - Sara Lee Corp., 1958-1991, 3 folders (Box 77)
  - Jos. Schlitz Brewing Co., 1956-1982, 1-3 of 9 folders (Box 77)
  - Jos. Schlitz Brewing Co., 1956-1982, 4-9 of 9 folders (Box 78)
  - Scholl Mfg. Co., 1958-1982 (Box 79)
  - Schwinn Bicycle Co., 1970-1981 (Box 79)
  - Sears Roebuck and Co., 1960-1992, 1-6 of 24 folders (Box 79)
  - Sears Roebuck and Co., 1960-1992, 7-12 of 24 folders (Box 80)
  - Sears Roebuck and Co., 1960-1992, 13-18 of 24 folders (Box 81)
  - Sears Roebuck and Co., 1960-1992, 19-23 of 24 folders (Box 82)
  - Sears Roebuck and Co., 1960-1992, 24 of 24 folders (Box 83)
  - Seven-Up Co., 1963-1988, 5 folders (Box 83)
  - Sherwin-Williams, 1972-1993, 3 folders (Box 84)
  - Smirnoff, 1987 (Box 84)
  - J.M. Smucker Co., 1972-1997 (Box 84)
  - Sonic, 1994 (Box 84)
  - Southland Corp., 1980-1997, 3 folders (Box 84)
  - Southwest Air, 1991-1995 (Box 85)
  - Spiegel Inc., 1983-1992 (Box 85)
  - Sprint Corp., 1986-1993, 3 folders (Box 85)
  - Std. Brands, 1974-1979 (Box 85)
  - Sterling Brewers, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 85)
  - Stokely-Van Camp, 1958-1980 (Box 85)
  - Stouffer Foods, 1971-1992 (Box 85)
  - Levi Strauss and Co., 1979-1992, 2 folders (Box 86)
  - Stroh Brewery Co., 1968-1988 (Box 86)
  - Sunbeam Corp., 1976-1981 (Box 86)
  - Sun-Maid, 1986-1989 (Box 86)
  - Supercuts, 1983-1990 (Box 86)
  - TCBY, 1989-1992 (Box 86)
  - Taco Bell, 1978-1991 (Box 86)
  - Teledyne Water Pik, 1967-1981 (Box 86)
  - Terson Co., 1974-1981 (Box 86)
  - Texas Instruments, 1976-1983 (Box 86)
  - Tootsie Roll, 1970-1984 (Box 87)
  - Toys R Us, 1975-1992 (Box 87)
  - Tropicana, 1991-1993 (Box 87)
  - Turtle Wax, Inc., 1967-1986 (Box 87)
  - UAL (United Airlines), 1972-1992, 2 folders (Box 87)
  - Uncle Ben's Inc., 1974-1984 (Box 87)
  - Unilever, 1989-1995 (Box 87)
  - United Dairy Industry Assn., 1984-1993 (Box 87)
  - United Parcel Service, 1982-1991 (Box 87)
  - U.S. Air, 1974-1992 (Box 87)
  - Video Storyboard Tests, 1982-1992 (Box 88)
  - Vienna Sausage Mfg. Co., 1978-1982 (Box 88)
  - Volkswagen of America, 1970-1992 (Box 88)
  - Walgreen Co., 1975-1990, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Wal Mart, 1981-1993, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Warner Lambert, 1967-1992 (Box 88)
  - Weight Watchers, 1973-1992 (Box 89)
  - Wells Rich Greene, 1971-1988 (Box 89)
  - Wendy's, 1976-1994, 3 folders (Box 89)
  - Whittle Communications, 1989-1992 (Box 89)
  - Wickes, 1977-1986 (Box 89)
  - Wilson Foods, 1972-1988 (Box 89)
  - Wimpy's, 1977-1978 (Box 89)
  - F.M. Woolworth Co., 1961-1990, 2 folders (Box 89)
  - World Book - Childcraft Int'l., 1965-1978 (Box 90)
  - Wm. Wrigley Jr. Co., 1970-1990, 2 folders (Box 90)
  - Xerox Corp., 1972-1994 (Box 90)
  - Zenith Radio Corp., 1976-1992 (Box 90)
  - Kraft Research Report card file. (Box 91)
  - Oversized Materials
    - Kraft, 2 folders (Box 92)
    - Oscar Mayer (Box 92)
    - Walgreen Co. (Box 92)
  - Vinyl Records
    - Kraft: 75th Anniversary Radio Special, 1978 (Box 92)
    - Oscar Mayer: Meatpacker Suite, 1980 (Box 92)
    - Oscar Mayer: Meatpacker Suite, 1980 (Box 92)